<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adham Omran</title>
    <link>http://adham-omran.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adham Omran</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://adham-omran.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://adham-omran.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adham-omran.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Me! Email Email me at adham.rasoul@hotmail.com!
You can also find me on  Instagram GitHub LinkedIn  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>http://adham-omran.com/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adham-omran.com/now/</guid>
      <description>This page lists what I am working on at the moment!
Data Analysis  Learning to become a data analyst, currently studying Applied Statistics by Devore.  System of Systems  Designing my own System of Systems for productivity and life management with the aims of a simple and pragmatic approach to living life.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning</title>
      <link>http://adham-omran.com/concepts/20210413192701-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adham-omran.com/concepts/20210413192701-planning/</guid>
      <description>Created: [2021-04-13 Tue 19:27] Modified: [2021-06-07 Tue 13:16]  Abstract My plans come in a hierarchical form, starting at any point in the chain can lead you to the other levels of planning. The entire form is as follows:
Planning Hierarchy   Vision: Highest level, least defined, most abstract, it&amp;rsquo;s where you want to find yourself, Example: Become a web developer.
  Roadmap: A set of projects that when done, accomplish part of a vision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study</title>
      <link>http://adham-omran.com/concepts/20210329182107-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adham-omran.com/concepts/20210329182107-study/</guid>
      <description>Created: [2021-03-29 Mon 18:21] Updated: [2021-06-07 Mon 14:19]  Abstract  Below is the detailed documentation of how I study, by that I mean the process of taking a source of information, converting it into notes, then state how to process these notes, mainly for spaced repition and Zettelkasten literature notes  Purpose of Material  For a piece of material to be worth studying, processing and memorizing, it must provide value to the learner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Write a Note That You Will Actually Understand • Zettelkasten Method</title>
      <link>http://adham-omran.com/literature-notes/20210519122312-how_to_write_a_note_that_you_will_actually_understand_zettelkasten_method/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adham-omran.com/literature-notes/20210519122312-how_to_write_a_note_that_you_will_actually_understand_zettelkasten_method/</guid>
      <description>source: How to Write a Note That You Will Actually Understand • Zettelkasten Method
Abstract  This is a summary of the original article, please read it before this one.  Write simple  Use paragraphs. Use short understandable sentences.  Write with explicit form  Since notes can describe different items, from a philosophical idea to a statistics concept, different types of notes can exit with different form or template for each (YASnippet is a possible effective solution here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Categories</title>
      <link>http://adham-omran.com/concepts/time-categories/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adham-omran.com/concepts/time-categories/</guid>
      <description>Created: [2021-05-06 Thu 22:05] Updated: [2021-06-07 Wed 19:14]  Abstract  This concept states that we should look at time in terms of its category in addition to its blocks (Deep Work Blocks) and roles (Roles). Simply, time can be seen as categories, the two main ones are Doing and Thinking. Thinking involves activities such as study, research and reading (Reading queue). Doing invovles anything action-oriented such as practice, writing for publishing (NOT note-taking or formulation), recording, composing, coding for a project (NOT reading guides)  Application  Use the 80/20 division of Doing/Study I want to use this on a weekly scale, assuming work weeks are 6 days, 12 hours a day (4 a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://adham-omran.com/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adham-omran.com/music/</guid>
      <description>Music Telegram Channel  Published music can be found here on telegram  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
