<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adham Omran</title>
    <link>http://adham-omran.com/concepts/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adham Omran</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://adham-omran.com/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Study</title>
      <link>http://adham-omran.com/concepts/20210329182107-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adham-omran.com/concepts/20210329182107-study/</guid>
      <description>:ID: 49bf7878-62a2-4c6b-8990-da59fa5e00fa
[2021-03-29 Mon 18:21] tags Deep Work Blocks, ,  Purpose, Framework and Workflow Abstract  Below is the detailed documentation of how I study, by that I mean the process of taking a source of information, converting it into notes, then state how to process these notes, mainly for spaced repition and Zettelkasten literature notes  Purpose of Material  For a piece of material to be worth studying, processing and memorizing, it must provide value to the learner, this value can come in many forms, but it has to provide it in some form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Categories</title>
      <link>http://adham-omran.com/concepts/time-categories/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adham-omran.com/concepts/time-categories/</guid>
      <description>Abstract  This concept states that we should look at time in terms of its category in addition to its blocks (Deep Work Blocks) and roles (Roles). Simply, time can be seen as categories, the two main ones are Doing and Thinking. Thinking involves activities such as study, research and reading (Reading queue). Doing invovles anything action-oriented such as practice, writing for publishing (NOT note-taking or formulation), recording, composing, coding for a project (NOT reading guides)  Application  Use the 80/20 division of Doing/Study I want to use this on a weekly scale, assuming work weeks are 6 days, 12 hours a day (4 a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Songwriting Workflow</title>
      <link>http://adham-omran.com/concepts/songwriting-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adham-omran.com/concepts/songwriting-workflow/</guid>
      <description>[2020-10-28 Wed 21:32]Framework Purpose  Describe my songwriting process for various genres. Describe how to navigate writing a piece of music from start to finish. Describe my recording and production process for various genres. Describe the mixing process. Describe the mastering process. Describe how to maintain multiple songwriting projects. Describe how to collaborate with other musicians. Describe how to promote and publish music. Describe how to arrange for a live show.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
